Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: OSTP, NSF, Rice, other subject files, 1964-2000
  - Senator Rockefeller, March 1, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Leon Fuerth, March 1, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Leon Fuerth (RE China), March 5, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Secretary Rodney Slater, March 5, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Media Briefing - Mitre Corp., March 9, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Lunch with Elgie Holstein, April 2, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Sir Robert May, April 26, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Meeting with VP Gore, May 5, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Holdren Briefing for Todd Stern, May 13, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Elgie Holstein, May 17, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Leon Fuerth, May 17, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Deputies Meeting (GMOs), June 7, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - NSTAC Executive Session, June 9, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Climate Change Event with VP Gore, August 2, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Budget Meeting with OMB and Science Leaders, August 10, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Podesta with University Presidents, September 22, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Cabinet Meeting notes, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Cabinet Meeting, November 22, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Cabinet Briefing, December 19, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Neal Lane's First Cabinet Meeting, November 10, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Cabinet Meeting, January 13, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - First Cabinet Meeting, February 23, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Meeting, June 3, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Cabinet Meeting, July 16, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet Meeting, August 5, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Cabinet Meeting, September 15, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet Meeting - Hurricanes Floyd and Gert, September 15, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Cabinet Policy Seminar on Y2K, September 18, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Cabinet Meeting, November 10, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Cabinet Meeting, January 19, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Cabinet Meeting (Podesta), March 16, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Cabinet Meeting, September 28, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - PCAST Meeting, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - PCAST Meeting, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 17-18, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 17-18, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 17-18, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - PCAST Meeting - OSTP GPRA Survey, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - PCAST Meeting - OSTP GPRA Survey, November 19, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - PCAST Meeting - OSTP GPRA Survey, November 19, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Presidential S and T Awards - Event Procedures (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Presidential S and T Awards - Event Procedures (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - OSTP Weekly Reports to the President, February 20 - December 18, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - OSTP Weekly Reports to the President, January 8, 1999 - April 21, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - OSTP Weekly Reports to the President, April 28, 2000 - December 15, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Transition Briefing Materials - OSTP (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Transition Briefing Materials - OSTP (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Transition Briefing Materials - OSTP (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Transition Briefing Materials - OSTP (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - A Report to the Congress - Science and Technology Shaping the 21st Century, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - PCAST Meeting, February 22, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - PCAST Meeting, February 22, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - PCAST Meeting, May 24-25, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - PCAST Meeting, May 24-25, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - PCAST Meeting, May 24-25, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 16-17, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 16-17, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 16-17, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 16-17, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - PCAST Meeting, December 9-10, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - PCAST Meeting, December 9-10, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - PCAST Meeting, December 9-10, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - PCAST Presentation / National Science and Technology Council Annual Report, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - PCAST Meeting, February 17-18, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - PCAST Meeting, February 17-18, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - PCAST Meeting, February 17-18, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - PCAST Meeting, May 18, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - PCAST Meeting, May 18, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - PCAST Meeting, May 18, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 14, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 14, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 14, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - PCAST Meeting, September 14, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - PCAST Luncheon, December 1, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - PCAST "Transition" (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - NSIA, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - NSIA, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - NSIA, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Affairs, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Cabinet Affairs, January-February 1999 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet Affairs, March-April 1999 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Cabinet Affairs, May-June 1999 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet Affairs, July-August 1999 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Cabinet Affairs, September-December 1999 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Cabinet Affairs, January-March 2000 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Cabinet Affairs, April-May 2000 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Cabinet Affairs, June-July 2000 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Cabinet Affairs, August-October 2000 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Cabinet Affairs, November 2000-January 2001 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Technology Division, February-December 1998 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Technology Division, January-May 1999 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Technology Division, June-December 1999 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Technology Division, January-May 2000 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Technology Division, June-December 2000 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Office of Intergovernmental Affairs - Ibarra, April 1998-July 1999 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Environment Division Weekly Report - Bierbaum, February-December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Environment Division Weekly Report - Bierbaum, January-May 1999 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Environment Division Weekly Report - Bierbaum, June-December 1999 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Environment Division Weekly Report - Bierbaum, January-December 2000 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - CEQ Weekly Report, April-December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - CEQ Weekly Report, January-December 1999 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - CEQ Weekly Report, January-November 2000 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Climate Change Weekly Report - Stern, October 1998 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Office of Environmental Initiatives Weekly Report - Ballentine, June 1999-December 2000 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - NSIA Weekly Progress Report, January-May 2000 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - NSIA Weekly Progress Report, June-December 2000 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - The 1996 National Science Foundation Authorization - Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Basic Research of the Committee on Science, U.S. House of Representatives, 104th Congress, First Session, February 22; March 2, 1995 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - The State of Science, Math, Engineering, and Technology (SMET) Education in America, Parts I-IV, Including the Results of the Third International Mathematics and Science Study (TIMSS) - Hearings Before the Committee on Science, U.S. House of Representatives, 105th Congress, First Session, July 23, September 24, October 8, and 29, 1997 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Departments of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development, and Independent Agencies Appropriations for 1995 - Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, 103rd Congress, Second Session, 1994 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Departments of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development, and Independent Agencies Appropriations for 1996 - Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, 104th Congress, First Session, 1995 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Departments of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development, and Independent Agencies Appropriations for 1997 - Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, 104th Congress, Second Session, 1996 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Departments of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development, and Independent Agencies Appropriations for 1998 - Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, 105th Congress, First Session, 1997 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Departments of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development, and Independent Agencies Appropriations for 1998 - Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, 105th Congress, First Session, 1997 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Departments of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development and Independent Agencies Appropriations, Fiscal Year 1995 - Senate Hearings Before the Committee on Appropriations, 103rd Congress, Second Session, 1994 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Departments of Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development and Independent Agencies Appropriations, Fiscal Year 1998 - Senate Hearings Before the Committee on Appropriations, 105th Congress, First Session (Box 61, Folder -)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, The Washington Court Hotel, September 23, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, The Washington Hilton and Towers, November 29-30, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, The Washington Hilton and Towers, November 29-30, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, J.W. Marriott Hotel, March 6-7, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, J.W. Marriott Hotel, March 6-7, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, J.W. Marriott Hotel, March 6-7, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, Washington Plaza Hotel, May 8-9, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, Washington Plaza Hotel, May 8-9, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - The National Commission on Mathematics and Science Teaching for the 21st Century materials, Jurys Washington Hotel, July 13-14, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF) - Index Listing for 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), January-December 1993 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), January-February 1994 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), March 1994 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), April 1994 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), May 1994 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), June-July 1994 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), August-September 1994 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), October 1994 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), November-December 1994 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF) - Index Listing for 1995 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), January-February 1995 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), March 1995 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), April-May 1995 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), June-July 1995 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), August-September 1995 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), October-November 1995 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), December 1995 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF) - Index Listing for 1996 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), January-February 1996 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), March 1996 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), April 1996 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), May-June 1996 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), July-September 1996 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), October-December 1996 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF) - Index Listing for 1997 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), January-February 1997 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), March-April 1997 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), May-June 1997 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), July-September 1997 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), October-December 1997 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF) - Index Listing for 1998 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), January-February 1998 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), March-April 1998 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Neal Lane Speeches (NSF), May-June 1998 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, October-November 1993 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, December 1993 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, January 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, February 1994 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, March 1994 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, April 1994 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, May 1994 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, June 1994 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, July 1994 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, August 1994 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, September 1994 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, October 1994 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, November 1994 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, December 1994 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, January-February 1995 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, March 1995 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, April 1995 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, May 1995 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, June 1995 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, July 1995 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, August 1995 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, September 1995 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, October 1995 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, November-December 1995 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, January 1996 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, February 1996 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, March 1996 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, April 1996 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, May 1996 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, June 1996 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, July 1996 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, August 1996 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, September 1996 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, October 1996 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, November 1996 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, December 1996 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, January 1997 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, February 1997 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, March 1997 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, April 1997 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, May 1997 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, June 1997 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, July 1997 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, August 1997 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, September 1997 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, October 1997 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, November 1997 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, December 1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, January 1998 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, February 1998 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, March 1998 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, April 1998 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation - correspondence, May 1998 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation, July 1993 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation - email, July-August 1993 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Rice to National Science Foundation - email, July-August 1993 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - National Science Board - Background Materials, Long-Range Planning, May-June 1996 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - National Science Board - Background Materials, Long-Range Planning, March-May 1997 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - National Science Board - 348th Meeting, May 6-8, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - National Science Board - 348th Meeting, May 6-8, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - National Science Board - 348th Meeting, May 6-8, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - National Science Board - 348th Meeting, May 6-8, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - National Science Board - 348th Meeting, May 6-8, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - National Science Board - 348th Meeting, May 6-8, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - National Science Board Minutes, February 1993 - May 1998 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - National Science Board Minutes, February 1993 - May 1998 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - National Science Board Minutes, February 1993 - May 1998 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - National Science Board Minutes, February 1993 - May 1998 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - National Science Board Minutes, February 1993 - May 1998 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - National Science Board Minutes, February 1993 - May 1998 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation Congressionals signed by Neal Lane, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation Congressionals signed by Neal Lane, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation Congressionals signed by Neal Lane, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation Congressionals signed by Neal Lane, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation Congressionals signed by Neal Lane, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1993 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation Budget Summary, FY 1993 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1994 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1994 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - National Science Foundation - Budget Overview, FY 1994 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - National Science Foundation Grant Proposal Guide, January 1994 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1995 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1995 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1995 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - National Science Foundation Budget Summary, FY 1995 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - National Science Foundation Guide to Programs, FY 1995 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - National Science Board - "Science and Engineering in the 21st Century", March 28-29, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1996 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1996 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1996 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - National Science Foundation Budget Summary, FY 1996 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - National Science Foundation Guide to Programs, FY 1996 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1997 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - National Science Foundation Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1997 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - Information for New National Science Board Members, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation Budget Summary, FY 1997 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation Guide to Programs, FY 1997 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation - Workforce Profile, mid FY 1997 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation - Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1998 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation - Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to the Congress, FY 1998 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation Budget Summary, FY 1998 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation Guide to Programs, FY 1998 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation Budget and Planning Document, October 1997 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation Budget and Planning Document, October 1997 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation - Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to Congress, FY 1997 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation - Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to Congress, FY 1997 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation - Justification of Estimates of Appropriations to Congress, FY 1997 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation Budget Summary, FY 1999 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation - FY99 GPRA Performance Plan, March 1997 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation - Backup Material for Congressional Hearings/Budget Request, FY 1999 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - National Science Foundation - Backup Material for Congressional Hearings/Budget Request, FY 1999 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - National Science Foundation - Backup Material for Congressional Hearings/Budget Request, FY 1999 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - National Science Foundation - Backup Material for Congressional Hearings/Budget Request, FY 1999 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - National Science Foundation - Backup Material for Congressional Hearings/Budget Request, FY 1999 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - National Science Foundation - Backup Material for Congressional Hearings/Budget Request, FY 1999 (Box 67, Folder 21)